I know I just remember like my wife
telling me she was pregnant the first
time it was like this really big
emotional dinner it was great by the
third time it was just a text message
that was it she sent me a picture of a
positive pregnancy test and I remember
looking at that thing just thinking like
wow I really hope she meant to send this
to somebody
else that's our number
three it will change you having k kids
will change you I learned that
especially cuz I have three young
daughters so I have become a feminist
100% with a wife and three young
daughters yeah of course I'm going to
defend women's rights when I own four of
them okay you remembered you're at a
comedy show
good I can't tell that joke at home I
cannot
cannot when our second child was born
all of our friends gave us the same
piece of advice right they said you need
to treat both kids exactly the
same exactly the same I was like that
parents don't do that you treat that
first kid the way you would treat like a
package that you marked
fragile you treat that next kid kind of
like how the UPS would treat that
package it's like fragile yeah good luck
throw
it I know exactly the same that's what
they said though it's like that you
can't I learned right away too that we
couldn't treat him exactly the same our
first daughter was born in New York City
at a hospital on Madison Avenue and we
named her madison that's cute our next
daughter was born at a hospital on
Martin Luther King
Boulevard yeah not exactly the same now
would be a weird first day of school if
I just Trot it in there and the
teacher's like who do we have here I'm
like oh this pale skin redheaded girl
this is Martin Luther King
shafu so no not exactly the same parents
all that means is like don't have a
favorite parents have favorites it just
changes constantly you know I just sort
of want to post the power rankings every
morning so my kids know where they
rank like Madison she's the oldest and
we had our first baby because we wanted
to have a baby right we had our second
baby because we wanted the first baby to
have a
sibling I don't know about you guys but
I think that I would rather find out
that I was an accident than a sidekick
right but then right before Christmas we
gave Madison one of those like little
toy cataloges so she could Circle one or
two things that she wanted for Christmas
and she just starts circling entire
pages of this catalog like I got to have
this whole page this whole page
both of these
Pages definitely that
page got to have everything on
these definitely want this page so
that's what she got for Christmas just
torn out catalog
pages and move down the power
rankings so then up next we have little
MLK she's a great kid love
her cute little toddler I was reading
her a story the other day and in the
middle of this story she just stands up
without a word walks straight to the
fridge pulls Madison's artwork off of it
walks straight to the trash throws it in
comes back and sits down and now she's
my favorite because that is
hilarious it's like something struck her
little brain while we were reading
Clifford she's like whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa this is a puppy okay well then
that is garbage
[Laughter]
but then her kindergarten teacher gave
her homework at Thanksgiving where she
had to list three things she was
thankful for number one was her mom we
all saw that coming fine number two her
siblings in a tie sure number three the
dog that is very hurtful because we do
not have a dog
she got halfway through her gratitude
list and then just turned into her wish
list right
away so she gets moved down the power
rankings again so now it's the baby at
the top cuz she's only you know one and
a half so what can a baby do right all
she's done for her first year of Life
almost two is just like crawl around the
house trying to eat her older sister's
toys that's
it I remember at one point my wife
turned to me she was like how many times
are we going to say sa this baby from
choking on something I was like
hopefully all of
them there are no days off in this
game the one thing that I don't like
about having babies is like being in
public like doing the baby voice always
feels super awkward but I think it' be
weirder to talk to a baby saying that
same stuff but just in your regular
voice it's like who has a little button
knows you do yes you do yes you
do who has a little button nose I'm
going to bite it
off that's how you get kicked out of the
mall right
away you are gone